...these cultures
and my accompanying notes...
(Sheldon:)...will give them a fighting chance.
(Leonard:)I'm going back to bed.
- Wait, put this in the bathroom.
- What for?
(Sheldon:)I need to measure
my fluid intake and output...
(Sheldon:)...to make sure
my kidneys aren't shutting down.
(Leonard:)I mix pancake batter in this.
(Sheldon:)No, that measuring cup
has always been for urine.
(Leonard:)You had time to make a label
for everything in this apartment...
...including the label-maker...
...but you didn't have 10 seconds
to make one that said, "Urine cup"?
(Sheldon:)It's right here on the bottom.
(Leonard:)Huh.
(Leonard:)I guess I owe the Betty Crocker Company
a letter of apology.
[COUGHING]